All right, they got water,
orange juice...
좋아, 물하고 오렌지주스...
사과주스 같은 것도 있네
...and what looks like cider.
Taste it.
마셔
Yeah, it's fat.
기름이잖아
지방을 마셨다구!
I drank fat!
I know, I did that two minutes ago.
알아, 나도 2분전에 마셨어
- 나 왔어
- 안녕, 양복 씨
Hey, Mr. Tux.
-Why aren't you dressed?
-We have a half-hour.
준비 안하고 뭐해?
30분 남았어
그건 4분 전 얘기지
7시 40분에 집을 나서야 돼
That was four minutes ago.
We have to be out the door at 7:40.
Relax, we'll be ready. It takes us
two minutes to get dressed.
걱정 마, 금방 준비해
우린 옷 입는데 2분이면 돼
그래도 지금부터
준비해주면 고맙겠다
I'd feel better if you
got dressed now.
-Okay.
알았어
안녕! 너무 섹시하다
Oh, look at you. All sexy.
Really?
정말?
- 자기야
- 안녕
-How come you didn't come over earlier?
-Because I'm a stupid, stupid man.
좀 더 일찍 오지 그랬어?
내가 멍청한 놈이라 그래
Hey, Ross, want some cider?
- 로스, 사과주스 줄까?
- 됐어
No.
So you're pretty close, huh?
준비는 거의 다 됐지?
화장도 했고, 머리도 했네
Makeup's on. Hair's done.
응, 옷만 입으면 돼
I just have to get dressed.
And that takes, what?
Just 6 or 7 minutes?
한 6, 7분이면 돼?
응, 우선 옷부터 고르고
Yeah. Once I figure out
what I'm wearing.
Glass of fat?
기름 한 잔 할래?
The One Where No One's Ready
What's the matter?
You nervous about your speech?
왜 그래, 로스?
연설할 게 신경 쓰여?
아니
Nope.
-You wanna hear it?
-Am I in it?
들어볼래?
내 얘기도 있어?
After I thank everyone
for donating to the museum...
박물관에 기부금을 내 준 분들께
인사 드리고 나서
... I sing a song about the wonder
that is Joey.
너 같은 짠돌이도 돈 냈다고
공표 할거야
안녕
안녕, 근사한데!
Hello! You look great!
Thank you. I know, though.
고마워, 나도 알아
You see this? This is a person
who is ready to go.
이런 모습이 바로 준비가
끝난 모습이지
피비, 넌 나의 별이야
Phoebe, you....
You are my star.
기부금 때문이니?
Well, you're my lucky penny.
All right, I took the quiz. And it
turns out I do put career before men.
퀴즈 풀어봤는데
남들보다 먼저 출세한대
일어나
Get up.
What?
뭐?
-You're in my seat.
-How is this your seat?
내 자리야
이게 왜 네 자리야?
I was sitting there.
- 거기 앉아있었으니까
- 그리고 일어났잖아
But then you left.
내가 스페인이라도 갔냐?
Well, it's not like I went to Spain.
I went to the bathroom.
You knew I'd be back.
화장실 갔다가
금방 올 걸 알았잖아
그게 뭐가 중요해?
아무 데나 앉아
What's the big deal?
Sit somewhere else!
The "big deal" is I was sitting
there last! So...
중요해,
마지막에 앉았던 곳이...
내 자리야
...it's my seat.
Well, actually, the last place
you were sitting was in there, so....
마지막에 앉았던 곳은
변기 아냐?
You guys, you know what?
It doesn't matter.
둘 다 그만 해
별거 아니잖아
You both have to go get dressed before
the big vein in my head pops.
둘 다 빨리 준비해
내 머리에서 김 나기 전에
- 그러니까...
- 알았어
I just have to do one thing.
It's not a big deal.
아직 해결할 일이 있는데
금방 끝날 거야
Get up!
일어나!
- 안녕!
- 왔니?
Phoebe, you look great!
- 피비, 정말 멋있다
- 나도 알아
All right already.
Are you gonna do magic?
오빠, 멋진 웨이터 같아
That's funny. Change.
칭찬 고맙다
빨리 준비해
-Hang on, I just got in.
-I don't care.
잠깐만, 지금 왔잖아
빨리 해, 8시 시작이야
늦으면 안돼
It starts at 8.
We can't be late.
"He could not, would not,
want to wait."
빨리, 어서 해
그냥 기다려
Our table is down in front.
My boss will be there.
우리 자리가 앞인데
관장님도 그 자리야
Everyone will see if we arrive
after it starts.
우리가 늦으면
행사 망치는 거야
누가 내 기름 먹었어?
Has somebody been drinking my fat?
Does this look like something a
paleontologist's girlfriend would wear?
고생물학자의 여자친구가
입을만한 옷이라고 생각해?
어쨌든 제일 돋보일 거야
I don't know.
You might be the first one.
-Rach, did you check the machine?
-No.
- 응답기 확인했니?
- 아니
Wait. This is the outfit that makes
my calves look fat. Never mind.
이걸 입으면 종아리가
굵어 보일 거 같아... 됐다
Well, Joey, I wrote
a little song today.
내가 곡을 하나 썼어
제목이 '일어나'야
It's called, "Get up!"
All right. You can have the chair.
알았어, 일어날게
정말?
-Really?
-Oh, my. Would you look at that?
이런...
이것 좀 볼래?
안녕, 나야, 지금 갈게
It's me, I'm coming over.
What if I'm already there
when you play this message?
이 메모를 들을 때
내가 거기 있으면 어쩌지?
좀 으시시하지?
Is that too spooky?
Hi, Rach, are you there?
It's me. Pick up.
안녕, 레이첼 거기 있어?
전화 받아
레이첼? 레이첼?
Rachel? Rach?
What?
왜?
Never mind.
그냥 불러봤어
모니카, 리차드요
전화 줘요
Monica, it's Richard. Call me.
이거 옛날 메시지야?
Is that message old or new?
최근 거야? 뭐야?
Old or new? Old or new?
It's definitely old.
Didn't you hear the double beep?
옛날 게 분명해
삐 소리가 두 번 났잖아
새로 온 거면?
What if it's new?
We agreed not to talk.
서로 전화 안 하기로 했지만
중요한 일이면 어쩌지?
It could be important.
Shouldn't I call him back?
전화 해볼까?
네가 이미 전화했었어
이건 옛날 거야
Honey, you did call him back.
It's old.
Yeah, see, Mon, listen. Listen.
모니카, 잘 들어
When Carol and I broke up...
캐롤과 헤어졌을 때
나도 같은 경험을 했어
... I went through the same thing.
You know what I did?
그래서 어쨌는지 알아?
I got dressed.
옷을 차려 입었지
Really, really quickly, okay? Okay?
아주 빠르게, 알았어?
어서, 어서
There we go. There we go.
You know what? Don't get up.
Just sit there.
됐어, 일어나지 마
거기 똑바로 앉아있어
I just hope you don't mind
my hand right here.
내 손이 어딜 가든
넌 신경 쓰지 마
건드리지 마, 화내지 마
건드리면 죽어, 화내면 죽어...
Not touching. Can't get mad!
맙소사!
이 지저분한 녀석들!
Oh, my God!
You rotten boys!
-Sorry, Phoebe.
-What am I gonna do?
미안해, 피비
미안해
이걸 어째?
안돼! 문지르면 안돼
뭘로 빼야되지? 뭘로 빼지?
Don't rub it!
What gets out hummus?
콩 소스는 뭘로 빼니?
Monica!
What gets out hummus?
If it is a new message,
what is he calling to say?
최근에 전화 한 거라면
왜 했을까?
Okay, thanks. Yeah, I'll try that.
되게 도움된다, 고마워
Maybe he called to say
you're obsessive and crazy?
너무 집착하지 말라고
전화했을걸
- 그럼 전화할까?
- 안돼
-So should I call him back?
-No!
No!
안돼!
-Fine, we'll both sit in the chair.
-Fine with me.
좋아, 우리 함께 앉자
I am so comfortable.
나도 정말 편해
나도 그래, 근데...
Me too.
In fact, I think I might be
a little too comfortable.
너무 편한 거 같다
그럼 안되지
Okay, we have 19 minutes.
I want you to go and change.
이제 19분 남았어
챈들러 먼저 가서 준비해
When you come back, Joey will go change
and he'll have vacated the chair.
그리고 나서 조이가 준비해
그럼 의자가 빌 거야, 됐지?
-Okay.
-All right.
알았어, 간다, 가
내가 돌아오면 다 내 자리야
Fine. I'm going.
When I get back, it's Chair City.
And I'm the guy...
난 사나이야!
소파에 앉을 사나이
...who's sitting in a chair!
이건 좀 너무...
피비, 그게 뭐야?
Is this a little too
Pheebs? What happened?
콩 소스가 묻었어
I got the hummus.
Oh, honey, we'll find you something.
You wanna wear my black jacket?
어쩌니? 방법을 찾아보자
검은 색 재킷 빌려줄까?
이 드레스와 안 어울려
-lt won't go with this dress.
-You're right.
맞아, 생각해보자
일단 벗어봐
-Well, let's just get you out of that.
-No, no, no. Not "out of that."
안돼, 벗지마
절대 벗지는 마
-Not "out" of clothes.
-Can Phoebe borrow your green dress?
피비한테 네 드레스 좀
빌려줄래?
전화했어
I called him.
- 정말?
- 응
Yes. I got his machine
and I left a message.
응답기가 받아서 메모 남겼어
괜찮아, 괜찮을 거야
But it's okay. It's okay...
일상적이고 가벼운 얘기였어
정말이야
... because it was, like,
a casual, breezy message.
It was breezy.
Oh, God, what if it wasn't breezy?
가볍게 안 들리면 어쩌지?
가벼운 메시지였을 거야
여기 분위기가 그렇잖아
How could it not be breezy? No.
Because you're in such a breezy place.
I got it. I'll play my message and
you guys tell me if it's breezy enough.
그럼 우리 함께 들어보자
응답기를 들려줄게
But how you gonna do that?
남의 전화를 어떻게 들어?
응답기 비밀번호를 알아
I know the code
to his answering machine.
Okay, Mon, I really don't think
this is the
모니카, 그러지 않는 게...
전화하니? 벌써 하는구나
Okay, you're dialing.
You are dialing.
Hi, this is Richard.
Please leave a message at the tone.
리차드입니다
메시지 남겨주세요
You have two new messages.
두 개의 메시지가 있습니다
What a cool job.
목소리 죽이네
"You have two new messages."
두 개의 메시지가 있습니다
Please pass the pie.
파이를 빨리 주세요
Hi, it's Monica.
I'm just checking in.
저, 모니카인데요
당신 메시지 듣고 전화했어요
I got a message and didn't know
if it was old or new.
옛날 건지 요즘 건지 몰라서
확인하려구요
So I'm just checking.
So let me know.
전화하든지 말든지 해요
가벼운 맘으로 했어요
Or don't. Whatever.
I'm breezy!
You can't say you're "breezy."
That negates the "breezy."
'가벼운 맘'? 너무 강조하면
반대로 들린다구
안녕! 나야, 어제 즐거웠어
이번 주말에 전화해 줘
Hola. It's me.
Yesterday was really fun.
Call me about this weekend, okay?
저런 게 가벼운 메시지야
Now, she sounded breezy.
He's seeing someone.
I can't believe he's seeing someone.
누군가를 만나고 있어
어떻게 그럴 수 있지?
확실한 건 아니잖아
-You don't know that.
-Well, whose voice was that?
그럼 그게 누구야?
Maybe it was his sister's.
Maybe it was his daughter's.
여동생이었겠지
아니면 딸이거나
Michelle. Of course!
Did it sound like Michelle?
미셸이다, 그래 미셸이야
목소리가 비슷하지?
Oh, great. It's starting to rain.
That'll make it easier to get a cab.
일 났군, 비가 온다
택시 잡기 좋겠다
It was Michelle.
- 미셸이었어
- 그래
It was definitely Michelle.
분명히 미셸이었어
Try Monica's green dress. If it
doesn't fit, wear my gray silk one.
피비, 따라가 녹색 드레스 입어봐
아니면, 내 드레스를 입던지
이런! 난 뭘 입지?
-Unless I wear it.
-You don't know what you're wearing?
아직 옷을 못 골랐어?
I'm just trying to look nice
for your big night.
자기한테 중요한 날이니까
예쁘게 하고 싶어
Yeah, which we have to leave for
in 12 minutes.
12분밖에 안 남았어
그럼 내가 골라줄게
Come on, I'll just pick
something out for you.
난 옷을 다 차려입었어
그런데 넌 아직이잖아
You'll notice that I'm fully dressed.
I, in turn, have noticed
that you are not.
So in the words of A.A. Milne,
"Get out of my chair, dill-hole."
어떤 소설에
이런 말이 나오지
내 의자를 내놔! 짜샤
알았어
Okay.
-What are you doing?
-You said to give you the chair.
무슨 짓이야?
넌 소파 얘기만 했지
쿠션 얘긴 안 했어
You didn't say anything about cushions.
They're the essence
of the chair!
쿠션은 소파의 핵심이야
맞아! 핵심을 가져간다
That's right! I'm taking the essence.
Oh, he'll be back.
돌아오겠지
방에 아무도 없네
Oh, there's nobody in the room.
-I'm sorry, I thought it looked pretty.
-That was a Halloween costume.
미안해, 난 그게 예뻤어
그건 할로윈 의상이잖아
Unless you would like me to go
as Little Bo Peep.
내가 양치기 소녀 옷을
입고 가면 좋겠어?
I didn't recognize it
without that inflatable sheep.
옷 뒤에 양 인형이
달려있는 줄 몰랐어
지금 기분 같아선
나도 과거로 돌아가고 싶어
Yeah, which, by the way, Chandler,
I would like back one of these days.
Rach, good! Listen, isn't this
perfect for me?
레이첼, 이거 봐
이러면 완벽하지?
Oh, it's perfect! But not for tonight.
좋아, 근데 오늘 모임엔
안 어울려
Of course, not for tonight.
Hi. I'm going to a benefit.
오늘이 아니라
자선 모임에 입을 거야
그래라
- 오늘 모임이 뭔데?
- 미안, 기분 상하지 마
Not for tonight?
What are you doing?
No, I'm sorry. We didn't mean it.
I love you. Breathe.
- 그래, 미안
- 사랑해, 사랑해, 진정해
We used them as pillows
when we went camping.
그 할로윈 의상
캠핑 갈 때 쓴 거 아냐?
What?
뭐?
The sheep.
양 달린 거
Hey, what you do on your own time....
그거야 너만 알지
Where's my underwear?
내 팬티 어쨌어?
뭐야, 뭐야?
팬티를 숨겼어?
-Come on, you took his underwear?
-He took my essence!
얘는 내 핵심을 가져갔어
잠깐!
Okay, hold on. Why can't you just wear
the underwear you're wearing now?
지금 입고 있는 팬티
그냥 입으면 안돼?
Because I'm not wearing
any underwear now.
난 지금 노팬티란 말야
Then why do you have
to wear underwear tonight?
그러면 꼭 팬티를
입어야 하니?
빌려온 턱시도야
It's a rented tux, okay?
I'm not gonna go commando
in another man's fatigues.
다른 남자의 그게 닿은 곳에
내 것도 닿으라구?
Then somebody's gonna have
to give somebody back his cushions.
그럼 누군가의 쿠션과
맞바꾸면 되겠네
Okay. You hide my clothes, I'm gonna
do the exact opposite to you.
내 옷을 숨겼지?
나는 정반대로 복수할 거야
그럼 내 속옷을 여기 저기
내다놓을 거야?
What, are you gonna show me my clothes?
정반대가 그거 밖에 없냐?
Hey, opposite...
...is opposite.
별거 아니네
He's got nothing!
Okay, I'm ready.
나 준비 됐어
Rachel didn't have anything I liked
but this ribbon.
레이첼 옷은 맘에 안 들어서
크리스마스 리본을 달았어
I thought, all right,
I'll be political.
정치 모임에 가는 것 같지?
-What are you supporting?
-Christmas.
어느 당 후원자니?
크리스마스 당
Hey, that's okay with me. Two down,
and I have exactly 12 minutes
내가 보기엔 괜찮아
둘은 준비 됐고, 12분 남았어
What?
내 시계가 죽었어
이 놈의 시계가...
My watch stopped.
My watch. Okay, see...
공룡 꼬리 안 움직이지?
...the dinosaur tail
isn't going around anymore.
몇 시야? 7시 33분
7분, 7분 남았어!
What time is it? It's 7:33.
I have 7 minutes.
I have seven minutes!
Which shoes should I wear?
The black or the purple?
어떤 신발이 좋을까?
검은 색? 자주색?
- 자주색
- 제발, 빨리 골라
-Just pick one, okay?
-Oh, okay, okay. The black.
알았어, 검은 색
Do you have black
with little strappies?
검은 색에 끈 달린 거 있니?
응, 근데 그건 바지에 어울려
바지로 갈아입을까?
Yeah. But those go better with pants.
Maybe I should wear pants.
Yeah, pants! What an idea!
Or better yet, go without pants.
바지 좋아! 아주 좋아
아니면 아예 바지를
입지 말던지
네 맘이 어떤지 모르겠지만
네 발에 맞는 걸로 신어
I don't know what you're doing,
but just get in there...
...and pick out any shoes
that fit your feet.
I don't care if they match.
I don't care if they make...
아니, 안 어울려도 좋아
발목이든 무릎이든
허리까지 올라와도 돼
...your ankles or your knees or your
earlobes look fat. Just do it!
- 그래도...
- 아냐, 그냥 신어!
Go in there, pick something out
so we can go.
얼른 골라 신고, 빨리 가자
-All right.
-Thank you.
알았어
고마워
I've got to call Michelle to see
if that was her voice.
미안하지만, 미셸한테 전화해서
아까 그 여자인지 알아볼 거야
미셸 목소리였어
It was. It was her voice.
Monica, I think you've gone over
to the bad place.
모니카,
그거 과대망상증이야
Hola.
안녕, 여보세요?
여보세요?
Hello? Hello?
-Okay. That was her, right?
-Definitely. Yeah.
좋아, 미셸이지?
- 그래
- 분명해
So there you go.
이제 됐어!
We're out of the woods.
I think I'll get dressed now.
이제야 맘이 편하네
옷 입고 준비해야지
-I'll get it.
-Okay.
- 내가 받을게
- 그래
Hi, Monica and Rachel's.
모니카, 레이첼 전화예요
Yeah, just a second.
Can I ask who's calling?
네, 잠깐만요
근데 누구시죠?
It's Michelle!
미셸이야!
발신자 확인을 했나봐
어서 받아봐
She must have that "caller l. D." thing.
You should get that.
Michelle?
미셸?
Yeah, that was me.
I dialed your number by mistake.
응, 내가 했어
실수로 전화했어
Just try to be
You're so sweet.
너무 고마워
그래, 우린 잘 어울렸지
Yeah, we were a great couple.
I know, I really miss him.
당연히 보고싶지
어떤지 알잖아...
Well, you know how it is.
It's just that....
너 그거 알아?
You know what's weird?
Donald Duck never wore pants.
도날드덕은 팬티 안 입어
But when he gets
out of the shower...
그런데 샤워만 하고 나오면
허리에 수건을 두르고 있더라
... he always puts a towel
around his waist.
I mean, what is that about?
왜 그런 걸까?
I only beeped in so I could
hear my own message.
그냥 내 메시지만
들어본 거야
I mean, that's allowed.
그건 괜찮아, 정말이야!
아버지께 말씀 안 드리면
정말 고맙겠어
I would really appreciate it if you
wouldn't tell your dad about
What do you mean, you don't feel
comfortable with this? We're friends!
무슨 소리니?
뭐가 불편한데 그래?
우린 친구잖아!
That bitch always hated me.
얘는 날 싫어해
다시 전화해야지
I'm calling her back.
안돼!
똑딱, 똑딱, 똑딱...
-Okay, fine.
-Okay.
- 알았어
- 그래
-She's got a phone in there, right?
-Okay, we're on it.
방에도 전화 있지?
우리가 들어가 볼게
I know it says "black tie optional"...
반드시 정장일 필요는
없지만, 그래도... 좀...
... but this may be pushing it a little.
I'm not gonna go.
나 안 갈래
You're not gonna go?
안 간다구?
No, I think I'm gonna catch up
on my correspondence.
어울리는 걸 못 찾겠어
How can you not be going?
어떻게...
안 간다는 말을 해?
I'm not gonna go.
안 갈 거야
안 가는 게 더 좋을 거 같아
So I think that will accomplish
the "not going."
You know, just out of curiosity
혹시나 해서 묻는 건데...
Ever since I was humiliated
and yelled at in front of my friends...
친구들 앞에서 날 망신 주고
소리 지르는데...
... I'm just, I don't know, not in a
very museum benefit-y kind of mood.
이런 기분으로는
박물관에 가기 싫어
알았어, 정말 미안해
소리친 거 미안해
Right. Well, okay. Okay.
God, I'm sorry. I'm sorry I yelled.
-That's fine.
-No, but you're mad.
- 됐어
- 아냐, 너... 화났지?
I'm not mad. I'm just not going.
화 안 났어
그냥 안 갈래
- 그냥 안 간다구?
- 응
-Right.
-Okay.
그래, 나... 난 가야돼
You know that I have to go, right?
So is it gonna be, like,
I'm abandoning you while you're upset?
그런데 자기가 화내면
세상에 버려진 느낌이야
-No.
-No?
- 그러지 마
- 그래?
-You're not upset about the yelling.
-Right. And the humiliating.
- 그럼 화난 거 아니지?
- 응
- 소리 지른 것도...
- 망신 준 것도
- 그래, 그것도 미안해
Well, of course, the humiliating.
그럼 우리 괜찮은 거지?
So we...
...we're okay?
-We're good.
-Right.
- 정말?
- 그래
됐어
- 자기야?
- 왜, 로스?
-Honey? I love you.
-Yes, Ross.
사랑해
Get away from that phone!
전화기 내려놔!
She's just getting dressed now.
이제 옷 입을 거야
난 왜 저런 소리를
들으면 흥분이 되냐?
Is it wrong that I was
totally aroused by that?
Okay, buddy boy, here it is.
어이, 친구, 날 봐
You hide my clothes,
I'm wearing everything you own.
네가 내 옷을 숨겨서
대신 네 옷을 다 입었어
Oh, my God!
세상에!
That is so not the opposite
of taking somebody's underwear!
속옷 좀 숨겼다고
그 따위로 복수하냐?
Look at me! I'm Chandler.
날 봐! 난 챈들러야
옷 좀 더 없냐?
Could I be wearing any more clothes?
Maybe if I wasn't going commando....
나 지금 노팬티인 거 알지?
껴입고 있으니 덥다
It's hot with all this stuff on.
이러면 덜 덥겠지?
다리나 쭉 뻗어 볼까나
I better not do any,
I don't know, lunges.
Okay, enough.
Enough with the lunging.
이제 복수전은 끝났어
그만 해, 지겹다
I'm sick of this.
I've had it up to here.
너희 둘, 못 참겠어
모임에 가지마!
Neither of you can come to the party!
삐치기는!
Jeez, what a baby!
로스, 화내지마
가서 옷 입고 올게
Way to ruin it.
I was just gonna go get dressed.
네 맘대로 해
The only person
I cared about getting dressed...
정작 같이 가고 싶은 사람은
안 간다고 난리라구
...is the person who's
not even gonna go.
레이첼, 미안해, 알지?
Look, Rach, I'm sorry, okay?
Look, I was a jerk, okay?
I'm sorry I yelled. I want you there.
내가 바보였어
소리 지른 거 미안해
너랑 같이 꼭 가고 싶어
I need you there.
어떻게 해야 지금의 내 맘을
알아주겠어?
What can I do to show you
how much I want you to be there?
You could drink the fat.
기름을 마셔봐...
Welcome to an adult conversation.
무지하게 어른다운 말이다
No, no, no.
Now wait a minute. Wait a minute.
아냐, 잠깐, 잠깐만 기다려봐
그 제안 괜찮은데
-That actually sounds interesting.
-What?
뭐?
I think you should drink the fat.
기름을 마셔봐
잘 한다!
Okay, if that's what it takes to
show you how much you mean to me...
알았어
소중한 너와 함께 모임에
가고 싶으니까 마실게
...and how much I want you there,
that's what I'll do.
그건 먼지가 많아
다른 컵으로 마셔
Let me get you another glass.
That's been sitting out.
I think this will be fine.
이것도 괜찮아
Okay, vanilla milkshake.
Just a vanilla milkshake...
바닐라 밀크쉐이크다
바닐라 밀크쉐이크...
...with chicken bits floating in it.
먼지가 둥둥 뜬...
Cheers.
건배!
안돼, 마시지 마
갈게, 갈게
No, don't! Okay, okay, I'll go.
I'll go.
You will?
정말?
You were really gonna do that.
진짜 마실 생각은 아니었지?
Well, yeah.
마실까?
You were gonna drink the fat.
진짜 마시려고 했어?
Let's see what else he'll do!
다른 것도 시켜보자
How about you get changed?
Give him his underwear.
넌 가서 옷 갈아입고
넌 속옷 돌려줘
I'll get a cab. I want everyone
downstairs in two minutes.
난 가서 택시 잡을게
다들 2분 안에 내려와
Monica!
모니카?
Stop it.
그만해, 그만
Stop it!
Ross went to get a cab, so we
지금 택시 잡는대
지금 나가
What are you doing? No, Monica, no!
뭐야? 안돼, 모니카
Hi, this is Richard.
저는 리차드입니다
You have three new messages.
세 개의 메시지가 있습니다
Not anymore.
이제 안돼
메시지가 삭제되었습니다
Message erased.
To record your message,
begin speaking at the tone.
메시지를 남기려면
삐 소리 후 말씀하세요
Hi, Richard. It's Monica.
안녕하세요? 모니카예요
오늘 좀 정신이 없었어요
Listen, I did something
kind of crazy tonight.
Maybe I'm getting my period
or something. I don't know.
생리전 증후군 같은 건가봐요
Anyway, I beeped into your machine
and I heard this message...
어쨌든...
우연히 당신 응답기의
메시지를 듣게 돼서 놀랐죠
...that freaked me out...
...and Michelle will tell you the rest.
미셸이 다 말해줄 거예요
미안해요
오늘 일은 다 잊어버리세요
I'm sorry, okay? And I hope that we
can just forget the whole thing.
잘 있어요
Your outgoing message
has now been changed.
인사말이 바뀌었습니다
Outgoing?
인사말? 인사말이라구?
안돼!
Did that say outgoing?
Not outgoing!
Hi, Richard, it's Monica.
안녕하세요? 모니카예요
오늘 좀 정신이 없었어요
Listen, I did something
kind of crazy tonight.
생리전 증후군 같은 건가봐요
Maybe I'm getting my period
or something. I don't know.
안돼!
-How did you do that?
-I don't know!
- 어떻게 한 거야?
- 몰라!
Goodbye.
- 끝났습니다
- 안돼!
택시 두 대 잡았어
왜들 안 내려와? 가자, 가
Okay, I've got two cabs
and no people! Go, go, go!
Maybe we can call the phone company
to change the message?
전화기 회사에 연락할까?
메시지를 바꿀 수 있을 거야
그이 번호를 바꿔 버릴까?
They could change his number.
I think after this,
he'll be doing that himself.
이번 일로 본인이 바꿀 거야
Rachel!
레이첼?
자기... 너무 근사해
You....
You look....
And I still have about
five seconds to spare.
5초 정도는 괜찮지?
That was about 7 seconds.
7초나 지났네
그럼 약간 늦었어
So we're a little late.
Come on.
- 어서 가
- 안돼...
Oh, and by the way....
- 참, 있잖아...
- 왜?
What?
I'm going commando too.
나도 노팬티야
Dr. Geller?
겔러 박사님?
-Sherman Whitfield, London lnstitute.
-What a pleasure.
- 셔만 윗필드입니다
- 네
- 런던 연구소에 있죠
- 반갑습니다
I was quite impressed with your
paper on pre-Cretaceous fossils.
백악기 이전의 화석에 관한
논문이 아주 인상적이었어요
Yes. It confirmed everything
I'd written.
제 논문의 확실한 자료가 됐죠
Excuse me.
실례합니다
- 안녕하세요?
- 네?
Hi.
Yes?
You're kind of sitting in my seat.
여긴 제 자리인데요
What do you mean, your seat?
당신 자리라구요?
-I mean, I was sitting there.
-But you got up.
제가 앉아있었거든요
하지만 일어나셨죠?
But I never left the room.
여긴 안 떠났어요
자리에서 일어났잖아요?
But you left the chair area.
All right, that's it.
Give me your underwear.
네, 됐습니다
속옷이나 조심하세요